<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WC2018</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">WC2018</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">WC2018</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">wc2018@faziodev.org</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">WC2018 Logo</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Log Out</string>

    <!-- Facebook application ID and custom URL scheme (app ID prefixed by 'fb'). -->
    <string name="facebook_application_id" translatable="false">1979098249022833</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">fb1979098249022833</string>
    <!-- Twitter consumer key and secret -->
    <string name="twitter_consumer_key" translatable="false">yCvNaEAzLOBNNVM4LByQj1D2b</string>
    <string name="twitter_consumer_secret" translatable="false">5DXw3BYSAN8v2PJR61ISbAInBtUay0UiPNuohRefvu5Ap5emzT</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="privacy_text">
        Normally, this would some huge blob of legalese that nobody would read.

        Instead, as I\'m a developer, this is going to be basic.

        The only personal info I get from the site your email address and name (when you log in with a third-party service.)
        Your email address allows me to connect accounts across Google, Facebook, and Twitter into a single account.
        Your name allows me to display it for the site/app and any groups.

        I am using Google Analytics to get metrics on the site.  If this makes you uncomfortable, feel free to block it.
        I\'m just looking for numbers and to see if anyone cares about this thing.

        Past that, I don\'t get any personal info nor do I want it.
    </string>

    <string name="terms_text">
        WC2018 is just for fun, should be free, and has no attached warranty.

        Again, this is in no way officially associated with FIFA or the 2018 FIFA World Cup Russia™.

        Soccer ball icon and "Football golden cup trophy" background made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com
    </string>
    <string name="overview_team_distribution">
    Teams are distributed in parties randomly, based on criteria set by the party owner.\nOwners choose from three ranking systems (FIFA Rankings, ELO Rankings, and a random ranking) as well as how many teams each player is assigned.
    </string>
    <string name="overview_scoring">
        Players are awarded points for their teams\' performance in the World Cup.\n
        • Each win: 3 points\n
        • Each clean sheet (shutout): 2 points\n
        • Each draw (tie): 1 point\n
        • Each goal scored: 1 point\n
    </string>
    <string name="overview_summary">WC2018 is a fantasy game for the 2018 FIFA World Cup Russia™.\nJoin one or more groups, get your teams, and compete against your friends!\nYou can create and join groups of anywhere from 2-32 people.\nLog in above to get started!
    </string>
</resources>
